(Howard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Would you care to play
an ocean-themed game I invented?
(Amy:)Sure. What is it?
(Sheldon:)It's called Food, Friend, Fight.
(Sheldon:)One of us chooses
three aquatic creatures,
(Sheldon:)and the other one must decide
which he would eat,
(Sheldon:)befriend, or battle.
(Amy:)So it's like Kiss, Marry, Kill.
(Sheldon:)What is that?
(Amy:)It's a game
where you're given three people
(Amy:)and you choose which one
you'd kiss, marry, or kill.
(Sheldon:)Well, my game is better, 'cause
instead of marrying someone,
(Sheldon:)you get to eat them.
(Amy:)Let's just play.
(Sheldon:)I'll start
you off easy.
(Sheldon:)Electric eel,
pufferfish, shrimp.
(Amy:)Hmm. Well,
(Amy:)I wouldn't fight the eel,
because I know
(Amy:)it can generate enough current
to kill a horse.
(Amy:)So I'd eat
the eel,
(Amy:)fight the shrimp,
and befriend the pufferfish,
(Amy:)because it would be nice
to have company
(Amy:)on those days I feel bloated.
(Sheldon:)Very well done.
(Amy:)Thank you.